YING LU WEB DEVELOPER

yinglu2641@gmail.com

3 (781)799-2641

Greater Boston Area

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Driven Web Developer with experience in Python, Object Oriented Programming, JavaScript, and RESTful APIs. Attained Google IT Automation with Python Professional Certificate, and Certificate of Web Development from Framingham State University. Strong detail oriented programmer, with specialties in communication, time management, and problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

WEB DEVELOPER

Dec 2021 - Feb 2022 | Open Avenue Foundation, Boston, MA

- Developed operational CRM system from the ground up
- Established database management system
- Oversaw team communication using GitHub, Slack, and Zoom

DOG TRAINER

Aug 2018 - Apr 2021 | Sit Means Sit, Easton, MA

- Adapted training methodologies to achieve proficiency in obedience and agility skills
- Specialized in aggression rehabilitation.
- Performed service demonstrations to increase client sales
- Transitioned employee scheduling operations to digital format

ADMISSION'S RECEPTIONIST

Sep 2015 - Oct 2016 | Guilford College, Greensboro, NC

- · Collated and input applicant information to office database
- Bolstered applicant outreach relations
- Aided scheduling and office operations

CERTIFICATIONS

GOOGLE IT AUTOMATION WITH PYTHON

6 course program, developed by Google to provide professionals with in-demand skills including Python, Git, and IT automation. A hands-on curriculum designed to teach learners to write code, with capability of automating tasks. Participants achieved 80% or higher on graded assessments and a strong foundation of Git and GitHub, troubleshooting and debugging complex problems, and applying automation at scale using configuration management and the Cloud.

CERTIFICATE OF WEB DEVELOPMENT

5 month course designed to provide technical skills and experience needed to build web applications from the ground up. Course material included coding fundamentals from industry-practitioner instructors, through development of applications, in addition to real- world experience in a co-op style project at a company while using in-demand technologies including JavaScript, Node.js, SQL, APIs.

EDUCATION

Guilford College, Greensboro, NC

Sep 2015 - Oct 2017

Concentration in Criminal Justice and Cyber Security

SKILLS

JavaScript	React.js	HTML5	Python	Django	Git
MySQL	Node.js	CSS	Postman	MongoDB	GitHub